const List<Map<String, dynamic>> pastParticipleSetUpExercise = [
  {
    "exercise_id": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "game_key": 6,
    "description": "Type past participles"
  },
];

const List<Map<String, dynamic>> pastParticipleSetUpQuestions = [
  {
    'question': 'hit',
    'answer': 'hit,hit',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'sing',
    'answer': 'sang,sung',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'go',
    'answer': 'went,gone',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 3,
  },
  {
    'question': 'throw',
    'answer': 'threw,thrown',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 4,
  },
  {
    'question': 'do',
    'answer': 'did,done',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 5,
  },
  {
    'question': 'run',
    'answer': 'run,run',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 6,
  },
  {
    'question': 'become',
    'answer': 'became,become',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 7,
  },
  {
    'question': 'lead',
    'answer': 'led,led',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 8,
  },
  {
    'question': 'take',
    'answer': 'took,taken',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 9,
  },
  {
    'question': 'fall',
    'answer': 'fell,fallen',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 10,
  },
  {
    'question': 'lend',
    'answer': 'lent,lent',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 11,
  },
  {
    'question': 'speak',
    'answer': 'spoke,spoken',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 12,
  },
  {
    'question': 'bring',
    'answer': 'brought,brought',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 13,
  },
  {
    'question': 'choose',
    'answer': 'chose,chosen',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 14,
  },
  {
    'question': 'freeze',
    'answer': 'froze,frozen',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 15,
  },
  {
    'question': 'lay',
    'answer': 'laid,laid',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 16,
  },
  {
    'question': 'rise',
    'answer': 'rose,rosen',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 17,
  },
  {
    'question': 'bear',
    'answer': 'bore,borne',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 18,
  },
  {
    'question': 'eat',
    'answer': 'aet,eaten',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 19,
  },
  {
    'question': 'win',
    'answer': 'won,won',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 20,
  },
  {
    'question': 'swim',
    'answer': 'swam,swum',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 21,
  },
  {
    'question': 'hit',
    'answer': 'hit,hit',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 22,
  },
  {
    'question': 'sit',
    'answer': 'sat,sat',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 23,
  },
  {
    'question': 'sleep',
    'answer': 'slept,slept',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 24,
  },
  {
    'question': 'shake',
    'answer': 'shook,shaken',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 25,
  },
  {
    'question': 'ride',
    'answer': 'rode,ridden',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 26,
  },
  {
    'question': 'lie',
    'answer': 'lay,lain',
    "exercise_key": "Game_6_ex_1",
    "question_id": 1,
  },
];